[
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "boy",
        "answer" : "garçon",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["garçon", "fille", "homme"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "city",
        "answer" : "ville",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["ville", "pays", "citoyen"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "livre",
        "answer" : "book",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["book", "paper", "notebook"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "maison",
        "answer" : "house",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["house", "garden", "school"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "merci",
        "answer" : "thank you",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["thank you", "they", "excuse me"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "teacher",
        "answer" : "professeur",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["professeur", "parent", "directeur"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "sometimes",
        "answer" : "parfois",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["parfois", "souvent", "jamais"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "sorry",
        "answer" : "pardon",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["pardon", "souris", "sourire"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "souvent",
        "answer" : "often",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["often", "sometimes", "never"]
    },
    {
        "category": "word",
        "question" : "s'il-vous-plaît",
        "answer" : "please",
        "possibleAnswers" : ["please", "welcome", "pleasant"]
    }
]